18         THE POOL                                   OF TEARS            Iq
came, " Oh ! the Duchess, the Duchess I    in a low, timid voice, " If you please, 
Oh ! won't she be savage if I've kept her  sir The Rabbit started violently, 
                                           dropped the white kid gloves and the fan, 
                                           and skurried away into the darkness as 
                                           hard as he could go.
                                            Alice took up the fan and gloves, and, 
                                           as the hall was very hot, she kept fanning 
                                           herself all the time she went on talking : 
                                           " Dear, dear ! How queer everything 
                                           is to-day ! And yesterday things went 
                                           on just as usual. I wonder if I've been 
                                           changed in the night ? Let me think : 
                                           was I the same when I got up this morn- 
                                           ing ? I almost think I can remember 
                                           feeling a little different. But if I'm not 
                                           the same, the next question is, Who in 
                                           the world am I ? Ah, that's the great 
                                           puzzle ! " And she began thinking over 
                                           all the children she knew that were of 
                                           the same age as herself, to see if she 
                                           could have been changed for any of 
                                           them.
waiting ! " Alice felt so desperate that    " I'm sure I'm not Ada," she said, 
she was ready to ask help of any one ; so, " for her hair goes in such long ringlets, 
when the Rabbit came near her, she began,  and mine doesn't go in ringlets at all ;
                                                                    c 2

